[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress voiced Princess Fiona in the Shrek movies?", "correct_answer": "Cameron Diaz", "incorrect_answers": ["Julia Roberts", "Jennifer Lopez", "Catherine Zeta-Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How much does Smokey owe to Big Worm in the movie Friday?", "correct_answer": "$200", "incorrect_answers": ["$225", "$150", "$100"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What book is said to be the most shoplifted?", "correct_answer": "The Bible", "incorrect_answers": ["Websters Dictionary", "Thesaurus of English Words  Phrases", "National Geographic Atlas of the World"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Earl Bakk and Clarence W. Lillehie invent in 1957?", "correct_answer": "Internal heart pacemaker", "incorrect_answers": ["Liquid oxygen jet fuel", "High Definition Television", "Artificial heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these television networks came first?", "correct_answer": "NBC", "incorrect_answers": ["CBS", "ABC", "Fox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This cat breed, developed by American breeder Ann Baker, is large and has blue eyes and soft fluffy coat with point coloration.", "correct_answer": "Ragdoll", "incorrect_answers": ["LaPerm", "Egyptian Mau", "Savannah"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Emerald is the birthstone for this month.", "correct_answer": "May", "incorrect_answers": ["September", "April", "July"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Forrest Gump, what were the last words uttered by Pvt. Benjamin Blue to Forrest, just before he died?", "correct_answer": "I want to go home", "incorrect_answers": ["I want my Mama", "Am I going to make it?", "What are we doing here?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the largest of the so-called terrestrial planets of the Solar System?", "correct_answer": "Earth", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Venus", "Jupiter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following types of brain cells amplify the neural signals and maintain homeostasis?", "correct_answer": "glial cells", "incorrect_answers": ["axons", "neurons", "spindle cells"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tag belongs to what 1973 movie?  \nWhere robot men and women are programmed to serve you for... Romance... Violence... Anything.", "correct_answer": "Westworld", "incorrect_answers": ["Blade Runner", "I, Robot", "Futureworld"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The head of John the Baptist can be seen in the Amiens Cathedral.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]